Eugene Opie Papers ca.1919-1971 Mss.B.Op3
American Philosophical Society
- Correspondence
  - Cornet and Zeibig Trust (Box 10)
  - Cornman, Oliver P (Box 10)
  - Cort, W W (Box 10)
  - Cory, Richard A S (Box 10)
  - Cotzias, George C (Box 10)
  - Councilman, W T (Box 10)
  - Cowdry, E V (Box 10)
  - Cox (George S.) Fund for Medical Research (Box 10)
  - Crawford, Bryce, Jr. (Box 10)
  - Crawford, Porter J (Box 10)
  - Cruchley, I J (Box 10)
  - Cruchley, I.J. Tuberculosis tests (Box 10)
  - Critcher, Katherine G (Box 10)
  - Cullahan, Robert (Box 10)
  - Cumming, Hugh S (Box 10)
  - Cummings, Frank B (Box 10)
  - Cummins, Lyle (Box 10)
  - Curran, Jean A (Box 10)
  - Curtis, Joseph C (Box 10)
  - Cushing, Harvey (Box 10)
  - Cutler (Box 10)
  - Cyclopedia of Medicine (Box 10)
  - Dahl, Lewis K (Box 11)
  - Dakin, H D (Box 11)
  - Dannenberg, Arthur M., Jr. (Box 11)
  - Dannenberg, Marion L (Box 11)
  - Daoust, Roger (Box 11)
  - Davis, Herbert L (Box 11)
  - Dean, H R (Box 11)
  - Davis, L J (Box 11)
  - Dawson, M Henry (Box 11)
  - Dawson, Percy M (Box 11)
  - Dean, Rollin C (Box 11)
  - Definition and Pharmacology of Inflammation (Box 11)
  - De Forest, Gideon K (Box 11)
  - De Gara, Paul F (Box 11)
  - Deitrick, John E (Box 11)
  - Denham, Sir Edward. Report of the Nutrition Committee, Jamaica. (Box 11)
  - De Schweinitz, George E (Box 11)
  - Deyrup, Ingrith J (Box 11)
  - Diabetes mellitus (Box 11)
  - Diagrams (Box 11)
  - Dick, D A T (Box 11)
  - Diethelm, Oskar (Box 11)
  - Dillon, S J S (Box 11)
  - Dinkins, Eugenie S (Box 11)
  - Dinkins, Henry (Box 11)
  - Di Pallo, Polly (Box 11)
  - Diptheria (Box 11)
  - Doane, Joseph C (Box 11)
  - Dochez, Alphonse Raymond (Box 11)
  - Dock, George (Box 11)
  - Dock, William (Box 11)
  - Doggett, R L S (Box 11)
  - Doisy, E A (Box 11)
  - Dole, Vincent P, Jr. (Box 11)
  - Dolman, C E (Box 11)
  - Dominquez, Rafael (Box 11)
  - Doolittle, S E (Box 11)
  - Dormer, B A (Box 11)
  - Drinker, Cecil D (Box 11)
  - Drolet, G J (Box 11)
  - Du Bois, Eugene F (Box 11)
  - Du Bos, René (Box 11)
  - Duckett Jones Memorial Award (Box 11)
  - Dumbries, Jamaica (Box 11)
  - DuMond, Jesse W M (Box 11)
  - Dungal, Niels (Box 11)
  - Dunning, Henry S (Box 11)
  - Du Pont, Irenée (Box 11)
  - Durham, E K (Box 11)
  - Dustin, Pierre (Box 11)
  - Du Vigneaud, Vincent (Box 11)
  - Dysentery (Box 11)
  - Easton, Ernest D (Box 11)
  - Edison, Thomas (Box 11)
  - Edsall, David L (Box 11)
  - Edwards, Dwight (Box 11)
  - Edwards, Herbert R (Box 11)
  - Edwards, Joshua L (Box 11)
  - Egan, George F (Box 11)
  - Ehrlich, Paul (Box 11)
  - Eisenstadt Health Center (Box 11)
  - Ekhart, Walter (Box 11)
  - Ekhart, W. District of Eisenstadt, Distribution (Box 12)
  - Ekhart, W. Family graphs, Eisenstadt (Box 12)
  - Ekhart, W. Reports of tuberculosis dispensary in Eisenstadt (Box 12)
  - Ekhart, W. Tables of Eisenstadt Clinic (Box 12)
  - Ekhart, W. Translations of files of Eisenstadt Clinic (Box 12)
  - Ekhart, W. Tuberculosis in the Bergenland of Austria (Box 12)
  - Ekhart, W. Die Tuberkulose im Bergenland Statistische Daten. (Box 12)
  - Elden, Harry R (Box 12)
  - Electrolytes notes (Box 12)
  - Elliman, Doublas L., & Company (Box 12)
  - Elliott, Jabez H (Box 12)
  - Elliot, R C (Box 12)
  - Elmer, Walter G (Box 12)
  - Emergency Medical Service Training School (Box 12)
  - Emerson, Haven. (Box 12)
  - Emerson, Kendall (Box 12)
  - Empire Conference on care and aftercare of tuberculosis (Box 12)
  - Engelbreth-Holm, J (Box 12)
  - England (Box 12)
  - Engler, E A (Box 12)
  - Episcopal Hospital Chest Clinic (Box 12)
  - Erlanger, Joseph (Box 12)
  - Ernst, Edwin C (Box 12)
  - Eshleman, F (Box 12)
  - Evans, Milton (Box 12)
  - Ewing, James (Box 12)
  - Experiments
  - Experiments no. 2 (Box 13)
  - Experiments no. 3 (Box 14)
  - Experiments no. 4 (Box 15)
  - Fan, J H (Box 15)
  - Farley, David L (Box 15)
  - Farrand, Livingston (Box 15)
  - Fatty degeneration - necrosis (Box 15)
  - Federal Bureau of Investigation (Box 15)
  - Federation of American Societies for Experimental Biology (Box 15)
  - Feminist Movement (Box 15)
  - Ferrell, John A (Box 15)
  - Fidelity-Philadelphia Trust Company (Box 15)
  - Fike, Winston (Box 15)
  - Fischel, Walter (Box 15)
  - Fischel, Washington E (Box 15)
  - Flahiff, Edward W. (Box 16)
  - Flahiff, E.W.: Annual report of activities in Jamaica during 1939 (Box 16)
    - Family graphs (Box 16)
    - Jamaican diary (Box 16)
    - Protective inoculation for tuberculosis, Jamaica (Box 16)
    - Report, cumulative, of tuberculosis studies in Jamaica (Box 16)
    - Report on tuberculosis studies in Jamaica, 1936-1938. (Box 16)
    - Semi-Annual report on vaccination studies in Jamaica (Box 16)
    - Tuberculosis in Jamaica, Reports (Box 16)
    - Vaccination studies in Jamaica (Box 16)
  - Fletcher, F. B. (Box 17)
  - Flexner, Helen Thomas (Box 17)
  - Flexner, Simon (Box 17)
  - Flinn, Waldo R (Box 17)
  - Foley, M P (Box 17)
  - Forbus, Wiley D (Box 17)
  - Forchheimer, Frederick (Box 17)
  - Forkner, Claude E (Box 17)
  - Fox, Herbert (Box 17)
  - Francis, Thomas (Box 17)
  - Frank Tourist Company (Box 17)
  - Fraser, Peter (Box 17)
  - Freund, Ernst (Box 17)
  - Freund, Jules (Box 17)
  - Freund, Jules. Sensitization and antibody formation with increased resistance to tuberculosis infection induced by heat killed tubercule cells. (Box 17)
  - Friedenwald, Julius (Box 17)
  - Fuller, Anna, Fund (Box 17)
  - Funk, Ian C (Box 17)
  - Fulton, John (Box 17)
  - Furth, Jacob (Box 17)
  - Gallagher, Constance (Box 17)
  - Garrison, Fielding H (Box 17)
  - Gass, R S (Box 17)
  - Gasser, H S (Box 17)
  - Gates, Thomas S (Box 17)
  - Gay, F P (Box 17)
  - Gaylor, H R (Box 17)
  - George, Lloyd. Why the Allies will win. (Box 17)
  - Georgetown Univ. Kober Lecture (Box 17)
  - Gifford (Box 17)
  - Gildersleeve Memorial Meeting (Box 17)
  - Gillette, H M (Box 17)
  - Gilman, Daniel C (Box 17)
  - Glenn, Frank (Box 17)
  - Goat (Box 17)
  - Goldwater, S S (Box 17)
  - Goldwater Memorial Hospital (Box 17)
  - Goldwater Memorial Hospital, Research Service (Box 17)
  - Gooch, Marjorie (Box 17)
  - Goodpasture, Ernest W (Box 17)
  - Gordon, Lincoln. (Box 17)
  - Gout (Box 17)
  - Graham, A H (Box 17)
  - Graham, A.H. Preliminary report of the tuberculosis study, Lee County, Ala. (Box 17)
  - Graham, Evarts A (Box 17)
  - Graham, Helen Tredway (Box 17)
  - Graham, R (Box 17)
  - Green, John (Box 17)
  - Greene, Charles W (Box 17)
  - Greene, Roger S (Box 17)
  - Gregg, Alan (Box 17)
  - Grimes, Robert H (Box 17)
  - Guy, Loren (Box 17)
  - Hackett, L W (Box 18)
  - Hall, Frederic A (Box 18)
  - Hall, J M (Box 18)
  - Hallinan, T J (Box 18)
  - Halsted, William S (Box 18)
  - Hamill, Samuel McC (Box 18)
  - Hamilton, Alice (Box 18)
  - Hamilton, Clare (Box 18)
  - Hamilton, G E (Box 18)
  - Hanes, Frederick M (Box 18)
  - Hargesheimer, Thomas S (Box 18)
  - Harkins, Henry N (Box 18)
  - Harned, F P (Box 18)
  - Harper and Row, Publishers, Inc. (Box 18)
  - Hart, P D'Arcy (Box 18)
  - Hartenstein, Paul B (Box 18)
  - Harvey Lecture, 1955 (Box 18)
  - Hatfield, Charles J (Box 18)
  - Hauf, Marie Gribl (Box 18)
  - Health Research Fund, Inc. (Box 18)
  - Heiberg, K A (Box 18)
  - Heiser, Victor George (Box 18)
  - Hektoen, Ludvig (Box 18)
  - Henderson, James S (Box 18)
  - Henry, Alfred (Box 18)
  - Henry, Barklie McKee (Box 18)
  - Henry Phipps Institute, Univ. of Penna. (Box 18)
    Scope and Contents note
    See also: Phipps Institute, and: University of Pennsylvania
  - Henry Phipps Inst. Study dispensary families, 1930 (Box 18)
  - Hens fed on polished and unpolished rice. (Box 18)
  - Hess, Alfred F (Box 18)
  - Hetherington, Hubert W (Box 18)
  - Heuer, George J (Box 18)
  - Hewson, R W D (Box 18)
  - Heyman, David M (Box 18)
  - Hinsey, Joseph C (Box 18)
  - Hirst, George (Box 18)
  - Histamine and its inhibitors (Box 18)
  - Hodgkin's disease (Box 18)
  - Hodgkin's disease in animals (Box 18)
  - Hodgkin's disease, reports (Box 18)
  - Hodgson, Violet H (Box 18)
  - Hoffnagle, James H (Box 18)
  - Holden (Box 18)
  - Holmes, Gordon (Box 18)
  - Holt, L Emmett (Box 18)
  - Hopkins, F D (Box 18)
  - Hopkins, J A (Box 18)
  - Hopkins, Johns (Box 18)
  - Hotchkiss, Ruth. Limited sociological study of population (Box 18)
  - Houston, David F (Box 18)
  - Howard, H H (Box 19)
  - Howell, Thomas (Box 19)
  - Howell, William H (Box 19)
  - Howland, John (Box 19)
  - Hoyt, Archer (Box 19)
  - Hoyt, A. The operation of the stereofluroscope (Box 19)
  - Huber, G Carl (Box 19)
  - Hudson, N Paul (Box 19)
  - Hueper, William C (Box 19)
  - Hughes, Anne (Box 19)
  - Hughes, James (Box 19)
  - Hughes, William (Box 19)
  - Humphreys, William Jackson (Box 19)
  - Hume, Edward H (Box 19)
  - Hungarian Medical Trade Union (Box 19)
  - Hunner, Guy L (Box 19)
  - Hurd, Henry Mills (Box 19)
  - Hydrogen ion concentration of the blood (Box 19)
  - Hydropic degeneration (Box 19)
  - Immunity (Box 19)
  - Inflammation (Box 19)
  - Inflammation in embryo (Box 19)
  - Inflammatory irritants - histamine - Rous and Gilding (Box 19)
  - Ingalls, Theodore H (Box 19)
  - Instructions for photomicrography (Box 19)
  - Internal health board: tuberculosis (Box 19)
  - International Cancer Research Foundation (Box 19)
  - International Clinics (Box 19)
  - International Health Commission (Box 19)
  - International Journal of Microbiology as Applied to Biology and Medicine (Box 19)
  - Interurban Club (Box 19)
  - Irwin, L Beaumont (Box 19)
  - Isaacs, Joyce (Box 19)
  - Isaacs, J. Alpha Roman Catholic Orphage (Box 19)
  - Jackson, Henry (Box 20)
  - Jacobi, A (Box 20)
  - Jacobs, Philip P (Box 20)
  - Jaffe, Rudolf (Box 20)
  - Jamaica (Box 20)
  - Jamaica: Alma Industrial School (Box 20)
  - Jamaica: Annual report of Kingston tuberculosis dispensary (Box 20)
    - Anti-tuberculosis league. Report (Box 20)
    - Business before the honourable legislative council (Box 20)
    - Central board of health: tuberculosis dispensary (Box 20)
    - How to improve life for the islands youth (Box 20)
    - Public Health: malaria control (Box 20)
    - Kingston tuberculosis dispensary, Report (Box 20)
    - Provisions in regard to communicable diseases (Box 20)
    - Study of tuberculosis - Rockefeller Institute (Box 20)
    - Tuberculosis (Box 21)
    - Tuberculosis dispensary of Kingston (Box 21)
    - Tuberculosis study (Box 21)
    - Gazette, Supplement (Box 21)
  - Jaquerod, Wie Verhäten Wir Die Tuberkulose. (Box 21)
  - Jarrett,William H (Box 21)
  - Jay, Augusta E (Box 21)
  - Jeanes Hospital (Box 22)
  - Jett, Viola V (Box 22)
  - Jobling, James W (Box 22)
  - Johns Hopkins University (Box 22)
  - Johns Hopkins University Medical School (Box 22)
  - Johns Hopkins University Program: An Inventory (Box 22)
  - Johns Hopkins University Medical School: Proposed pathological institute (Box 22)
  - Johns Hopkins University. School of Hygiene and Public Health (Box 22)
  - Johnson, Ben (Box 22)
  - Jones, Albert L (Box 22)
  - Jones, Harold W (Box 22)
  - Jordan, E.O. Impressions of Health Conditions in America (Box 22)
  - Journal of Experimental Medicine (Box 22)
  - Journal of the American Medical Association (Box 22)
  - Kabat, Elvin A (Box 22)
  - Kahn, Reuben L (Box 22)
  - Karnovsky, Manfred L (Box 22)
  - Karsner, Howard T (Box 22)
  - Karsner, H. Western Reserve Univ. School of Medicine, department of pathology (Box 22)
  - Kato, Toyojiro (Box 22)
  - Kaufman, Charles J (Box 22)
  - Kelly, Howard A (Box 22)
  - Kemp, N L (Box 22)
  - Keppel, Frederick P (Box 22)
  - Kernan, Francis (Box 22)
  - Kerr, J Austin (Box 22)
  - Keyser, William Brent. (Box 22)
  - Keyes, Edward L (Box 22)
  - Khan, Zorab A (Box 22)
  - Kidd, Maudine A (Box 22)
  - Kidney (Box 22)
  - Kiehl, L (Box 22)
  - Kilpatrick, Martin (Box 22)
  - Kilpatrick, Mary (Box 22)
  - King, C G (Box 22)
  - King, Pao Zan (Box 22)
  - Kirkland, J H (Box 22)
  - Klotz, Walter C (Box 22)
  - Knopf, S Adolphus (Box 22)
  - Kohlberg, Alfred (Box 23)
  - Kohlberg, A. Visit to China, 1943 (Box 23)
  - Korns, John H (Box 23)
  - Korns, J.H. Report of Bureau of Tuberculosis Cattaraugus County, Dept. of Health (Box 23)
  - Kramer, S P (Box 23)
  - Krumbhaar, Edward B (Box 23)
  - Laboratory notes - Misc. (Box 23)
  - Laboratory notes - Rat experiments (Box 23)
  - Laboratory of the Henry Phipps Institute (Box 23)
  - Ladd, William S (Box 23)
  - Laennec Society (Box 23)
  - Lambert, Robert A (Box 23)
  - Lancefield, D E (Box 23)
  - Lancefield, Rebecca (Box 23)
  - Landau, William M (Box 23)
  - Landis, Eugene M (Box 23)
  - Landis, H R M (Box 23)
  - Larson, Burneice (Box 23)
  - Laussig, Albert E (Box 23)
  - Lawrence, G F (Box 23)
  - Lea & Febiger (Box 23)
  - Leach, Charles N (Box 23)
  - Leach, C.N. Tuberculosis in the Eisenstadt district of Bergenland, Austria (Box 23)
  - Leach, C.N. Ueber Beziehungen Zwischen Schicktest, Antitoxintiter und Diptherieempfäng-lichkeit. (Box 23)
  - Leathers, Waller S (Box 23)
  - Lee, Frederic T (Box 23)
  - Lee, John F (Box 23)
  - Lefevre, Egbert (Box 23)
  - Leukemia (Box 24)
  - Leukemia Fund (Box 24)
  - Leukemia Research Fund (Box 24)
  - Leukemia Lyphoma Research fund (Box 24)
  - Leukemia. Report on recent literature concerning treatment (Box 24)
  - Levine, Samuel Z (Box 24)
  - Lewis, Paul (Box 24)
  - Lewis, Sarah (Box 24)
  - Lewis, Sir Thomas (Box 24)
  - Lewis, Warren H (Box 24)
  - Lewittes, Mrs. David (Box 24)
  - Li, W M (Box 24)
  - Lim, Robert K S (Box 24)
  - Linell, Eric A (Box 24)
  - Linton, R W (Box 24)
  - Linton, R.W. Effect of immunization on the course of experimental tuberculosis in the ribbit. (Box 24)
  - Lippincott, J. B., Company (Box 24)
  - Liu, J Heng (Box 24)
  - Liu, P Y (Box 24)
  - Liver, Active transport; electrolytes (Box 24)
    - Animo acids (Box 24)
    - Autolysis; anoxia; kidney urea; pancreas; microanalysts (Box 24)
    - Cocaine (Box 24)
    - Denaturation of protiens of skin; histology changes in skin (Box 24)
    - Dry weight and water content (Box 24)
    - Electrolytes (Box 24)
    - in K-Ringer Oxygenation Ph of media (Box 24)
    - Method of oxygen supply in relation to water movement; urea formation in vitro (Box 24)
    - Permability of liver and kidney...; water intake (Box 24)
    - Permability to water of Heparin (Box 24)
    - Water content...; venous occlusion; cocaine (Box 24)
    - Water intake...; electrolytes (Box 24)
    - Water movement...; oxygen equilibration (Box 24)
    - Water movement and temperature; reversal of water exchange (Box 24)
  - Lobenstine, Edwin C (Box 24)
  - Lockwood, William W (Box 24)
  - Loeb, Leo (Box 24)
  - Long, Esmond R (Box 24)
  - Lord, Paul E (Box 24)
  - Lotos Club (Box 24)
  - Loudon Park Cemetery (Box 24)
  - Lough, Walter (Box 24)
  - Lund, Wallace (Box 24)
  - Lurie, Max B (Box 24)
  - Lyle, Floyd (Box 24)
  - Lyman, David R (Box 24)
  - -Lymphoma - miscellaneous notes (Box 24)
  - McCain (Box 25)
  - MacCall, W G (Box 25)
  - MacCallum, William G. A New Microtome: The Pathological Laboratory of Johns Hopkins University. (Box 25)
  - Mc Carthy, Daniel J (Box 25)
  - McClung, C E (Box 25)
  - McConaughy, James L (Box 25)
  - McCree, Thomas (Box 25)
  - MacCullun, W G (Box 25)
  - McDonald, Ellice (Box 25)
  - McDonnell, R A (Box 25)
  - McFadden, William M (Box 25)
  - McGraw-Hill Book Company (Box 25)
  - McJunkin, Frank Adam (Box 25)
  - McKenzie, R Tait (Box 25)
  - McKinley, E B (Box 25)
  - McPhedran, F Maurice (Box 25)
  - McPhedran, F.M. Clinical significance of latent pulmonary Tuberculosis (Box 25)
  - Macy, Josiah, Jr., Foundation (Box 25)
  - Madsen, Theodore (Box 25)
  - Mall, F P (Box 25)
  - Mallinckrodt, Edward, Jr. (Box 25)
  - Mallory, Frank B (Box 25)
  - Manhattan Convalescent Serum Laboratory (Box 25)
  - Manning, Margaret (Box 25)
  - Manwaring, W H (Box 25)
  - Mariette, Ernest S. Tuberculosis: Analysis of, among nurses (Box 25)
  - Mark, D D (Box 25)
  - Marshall, Charles C (Box 25)
  - Marshall, Harry T (Box 25)
  - Martin, Charles J (Box 25)
  - Maryland, Medical and Chirurgical Faculty of (Box 25)
  - Mason, Max (Box 25)
  - Matthaey, Alexander (Box 25)
  - Mauske, Elizabeth (Box 25)
  - Maxcy, Kenneth F (Box 25)
  - Mayer, John. Infarction of the myocardium (Box 25)
  - Mayo, C H (Box 25)
  - Meader, R G (Box 25)
  - Meakins, Jonathan Campbell (Box 25)
  - Medical Association of the Greater City of New York (Box 25)
  - Medical Clinics of North America (Box 25)
  - Medical College of Ohio (Box 25)
  - Medical Journal Club (Box 25)
  - Medical Science and the Routine of Living (Box 25)
  - Medical Searchlight: Tuberculosis (Box 25)
  - Medical Society for the State of New York (Box 25)
  - Meeker, George (Box 25)
  - Meiller, Fred H (Box 25)
  - Meleney, Frank (Box 25)
  - Meltzer, S J (Box 25)
  - Memory (Box 25)
  - Menkin, Valy (Box 25)
  - Menkin, V. Biology of inflammation. (Box 25)
  - Menkin, V. Diabetes and inflammation (Box 25)
  - Mentz von Krogh (Box 25)
  - Mercado, Rose de (Box 26)
  - Merkle, Hildegarde A (Box 26)
  - Mesenteric sclerosis...rat (Box 26)
  - Meyer, Adolf (Box 26)
  - Middlebrook, Gardner (Box 26)
  - Middleton-Goldsmith Lecture (Box 26)
  - Miesen, Sarah A (Box 26)
  - Milholland Ashenheim & Stone (Box 26)
  - Millbank Memorial Fund, Advisory Board (Box 26)
  - Miller, Benjamin F (Box 26)
  - Miller, C Philip (Box 26)
  - Miller, James Alex (Box 26)
  - Miller, Sydney R (Box 26)
  - Miller, T Grier (Box 26)
  - Miller, W O (Box 26)
  - Millikan, Robert A (Box 26)
  - Mills, E De Long (Box 26)
  - Milstein, S W (Box 26)
  - Minot, George Richards (Box 26)
  - Mirsky (Box 26)
  - Miscellaneous notes (Box 26)
  - Report of mobile home unit for study of tuberculosis (Box 26)
  - Moe, Henry Allen (Box 26)
  - Morgan County (Ill.) Medical Society (Box 26)
  - Montreal, Canada (Box 26)
  - Moodie, Roy L (Box 26)
  - Moore, Robert A (Box 26)
  - Form and substance in medical education, Moore, Robert A. (Box 26)
  - To Join Cornell Medical Faculty, Moore, Robert A. (Box 26)
  - Travelogues, Moore, Robert A. (Box 26)
  - Moore, Stanford (Box 26)
  - Morrison, Sir William (Box 27)
  - Mosby, C V (Box 27)
  - Moses, Jacob M (Box 27)
  - Mu Chapter Phi Beta Pi (Box 27)
  - Muckenfuss, Ralph (Box 27)
  - Mudd, Harvey G (Box 27)
  - Mudd, Stuart (Box 27)
  - Mäller, Friedrich (Box 27)
  - Mäller, George P (Box 27)
  - Muench, Hugo (Box 27)
  - Mumford, Edward (Box 27)
  - Munger, Bryce L (Box 27)
  - Munro, W T (Box 27)
  - Murphy, Francis T (Box 27)
  - Murphy, George E (Box 27)
  - Murphy, J Harry (Box 27)
  - Murphy, James B (Box 27)
  - Musacchia, X J (Box 27)
  - Mustard, Harry S (Box 27)
  - Muwin (Box 27)
  - Myers, Burton Dorr (Box 27)
  - Nakai, George S (Box 27)
  - National Academy of Sciences (Box 27)
  - National Aeronautics and Space Administration (Box 27)
  - National Association for the Prevention of Tuberculosis (Box 27)
  - National Ass'n. for Prevention of TB: Committee on research (Box 27)
  - National Cancer Institute (Box 27)
  - National Defense Research Committee (Box 27)
  - National Jewish Hospital (Box 27)
  - National Research Council (Box 27)
  - National Science Foundation (Box 27)
  - National Tuberculosis Association (Box 27)
  - National Tuberculosis Association. Advisory Committee on Social Research. (Box 28)
    - Advisory Committee on Social Research. (Box 28)
    - Budget and program for 1939 (Box 28)
    - Bulletins of (Box 28)
    - Committee on medical research (Box 28)
    - Committee on preventoria (Box 28)
    - Future program committee (Box 28)
    - Program committee (Box 28)
  - Neander, Gustaf (Box 28)
  - Necrosis (Box 28)
  - Neill, James M (Box 28)
  - Neistadt, I. Summary of and comment on the report on stereofluoroscope made to Dr. Opie by (Box 28)
  - Nelson, Thomas, and Sons (Box 28)
  - Neoplastic disease - Rockefeller Institute (Box 28)
  - Nettleship, Anderson (Box 28)
  - New York Academy of Medicine (Box 28)
  - New York Academy of Sciences (Box 28)
  - New York. Agreement between city of New York and public health research institute (Box 28)
  - New York Association of Tuberculosis Clinics (Box 28)
  - New York Bacteriological Club (Box 28)
  - New York City Department of Health (Box 28)
  - New York City Public Health Research Institute (Box 28)
  - New York Department of Health (Box 28)
  - New York Department of Hospitals of the City of New York: Research Division of Chronic Diseases (Box 28)
  - New York Hospital (Box 28)
  - New York Hospital. Board of Governors (Administrative Board) (Box 28)
  - New York Hospital Drug Letter (Box 28)
  - New York Hospital: Informational Bulletin (Box 28)
  - New York Hospital: Instructions for House Staff (Box 28)
  - New York Hospital: Its Program (Box 28)
  - New York Hospital: Medical Board (Box 28)
  - NYH: Pamplets (Box 28)
  - New York Hospital: Pulmonary Service (Box 28)
  - New York Hospital: Syphilis Clinic (Box 28)
  - New York Hospital Tuberculosis clinic (Box 28)
  - New York Hospital and Cornell University: Agreement between (Box 28)
  - New York Hospital: Report from department of pathology (Box 28)
  - New York Hospital: Pulmonary service (Box 28)
  - New York Pathological Society (Box 28)
  - New York Society of Tropical Medicine (Box 28)
  - New York State. Anti-vivisection bill (Box 28)
  - New York Tuberculosis and Health Association. (Box 28)
  - New York World's Fair (Box 28)
  - New Yorker article (Box 28)
  - Nichols, Joseph L (Box 28)
  - Nitzsche, George (Box 28)
  - Nobel Prize Committee (Box 28)
  - Noguchi, Hideyo (Box 28)
  - Normal and pathological movement of water in tissues and its relation to the colligative properties of solutions and to inflammation. (Box 28)
  - Norris, James (Box 28)
  - North Eastern Dispensary (Box 28)
  - Norton, Mrs. Charles F (Box 28)
  - Notebook: No.5: Cortone neoantergan colchicine (Box 29)
  - Notebook: No.6: Inflammation Colligative Properties Source (Box 29)
  - Notebook: Events (Box 29)
  - Notebook: Miscellaneous (Box 29)
  - Notebook: Pancreas, Island of L (Box 29)
  - Notebook: U.S. Army - medical notes. (Box 29)
  - Notes: (Box 29)
    - Acute Pancreatic Necrosis (Box 29)
    - Alloxan Diabetes (Box 29)
    - Animo acids (Box 29)
    - Bacterial infection (Box 29)
    - Bardeen (Box 30)
    - Broncho-pneumonia (Box 30)
    - Chromates (Box 30)
    - Colligative properties - see Resin (Box 30)
    - Congenital syphilis (Box 30)
    - Disturbance of iron metabolism, hemogloben transformation (Box 30)
    - Duodenal ulcer, 1938 (Box 30)
    - Dyes in relation to Islands of Langerhams and glomeruli of kidneys (Box 30)
    - Electrolyte (Box 30)
    - Experimental vascular disease (Box 30)
    - Freezing and melting point of liver (Box 30)
    - Gelatin collagen (Box 30)
    - High school and college (Box 30)
    - Histology - perfused human spleen (Box 30)
    - History of diabetes (Box 30)
    - Hydrosis (Box 30)
    - Hypertension (Box 30)
    - Infection with staphylococci (Box 30)
    - Isoelectric constants (Box 30)
    - Klein, Dr. (Box 30)
    - Leprosy (Box 30)
    - Lesions of Islands of Langerhams (Box 30)
    - Lobar pneumonia (Box 30)
    - Melanosis (Box 30)
    - Mesenteric arterial sclerosis (Box 30)
    - Milovan (Box 30)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 30)
    - "Morbid" anatomy and physiology (Box 30)
    - Necrosis references to denaturation of proteins (Box 30)
    - Oedema (Box 30)
    - Phosphatase (Box 30)
    - Polypeptides (Box 30)
    - Proteins - globulin (Box 30)
    - Reason and science (Box 30)
    - Synthetic-resin ion exchange, Myers (Box 30)
    - Tissue respiration (Box 30)
    - Urea and other agents tested (Box 30)
    - Zones of liver lobule (Box 30)
  - Notes and references: denaturation of protein (Box 30)
  - Nuttall, George H F (Box 30)
  - Nyhus, Lloyd M (Box 30)
  - Ochsner, Alton (Box 31)
  - Ochsner, Edward H. Further observations in the use of colloidal gold in inoperable cancer (Box 31)